<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vishwa Shah</title>
    <link>https://vishwa35.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Vishwa Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 01:10:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vishwa35.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://vishwa35.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 01:10:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwa35.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science major at Georgia Tech, graduating in December 2019
A driven, goal oriented computer scientist with a strong interest in data science and product development. I&amp;rsquo;m particularly intruiged by applications of machine learning in automating driving and optimizing transportation at large. I derive excitement from working on products that have tangible impacts on the quality of people&amp;rsquo;s lives, enabling them to focus their time on the more important interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://vishwa35.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 01:10:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwa35.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>@vpfbot (slackbot)   Slackbot built to streamline processes I encounter as Vice President of Finance for gtakpsi.
Python Slack API Heroku   StreetLens   Traces the route of Google Maps Directions via HoloLens | HoloHack 2016
Google Maps API Google Places API C# Unity HoloLens  
charles   HackGT 2018 Project: comparative analysis of tweets and reddit threads
Python Flask Data Science  
osquery   Fixing an int truncation error</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://vishwa35.github.io/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 01:10:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwa35.github.io/resume/</guid>
      <description>Download PDF
Education Georgia Institute of Technology Aug 2016 – Dec 2019 | Atlanta, GA
 B.S. in Computer Science (Intelligence and Information Internetworks), Honors Program GPA: 3.68 Affiliations: Alpha Kappa Psi (Business Fraternity), Ramblin’ Raas (Nationally Competitive Dance Team) Relevant Coursework: Machine Learning, Robotics and Perception, Algorithms, Intro to Artificial Intelligence, Intro to Computer Systems and Networks, Computer Organization and Programming, Probability and Statistics, Discrete Math, Linear Algebra, Multivariable Calculus, Data Structures/Algorithms  Experience Software Engineering Intern | Lyft, Core Datastores Jan 2019 - Apr 2019 (CURRENT) | Seattle, WA</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>