<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>linkedin on Vishwa Shah</title>
    <link>https://vishwashah.me/tags/linkedin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in linkedin on Vishwa Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:13:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vishwashah.me/tags/linkedin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Working across the pond</title>
      <link>https://vishwashah.me/blog/medium/across-the-pond/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwashah.me/blog/medium/across-the-pond/</guid>
      <description>This summer was filled with unknowns.
London, a city I knew no one in, on a continent in which I’d never left an airport. Palantir , where I’d intern as a forward deployed software engineer — I knew it’d be something different, but not exactly how.
These unknowns led to quite a bit of discovery. I was able to reflect on my place in the world and interface with people of all kinds of backgrounds and attitudes on life, careers, and politics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduating? Me? Not yet.</title>
      <link>https://vishwashah.me/blog/medium/graduating-me-not-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwashah.me/blog/medium/graduating-me-not-yet/</guid>
      <description>Last August I realized I would graduate in May — earlier than expected. I wasn’t mentally prepared; I didn’t know what I wanted to pursue career-wise. So I figured, another internship? I learned a ton this winter while at Lyft. My work was primarily related to data pipelines, and with the mentorship from Dan Fan and Ikramul Haq (and great feedback culture!) I strengthened my ability to evaluate technical design decisions, communicate across teams, and build solid services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interning at Redfin</title>
      <link>https://vishwashah.me/blog/medium/interning-at-redfin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 15:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwashah.me/blog/medium/interning-at-redfin/</guid>
      <description>Engaging homeowners without really knowing what it’s like to be one Nine months ago, I got on a call with my future manager to talk about the scope of the team and understand if it’d be a good fit. Owner Engagement focuses on making Redfin resourceful for homeowners in an effort to retain their interest and ultimately convert owners to sellers.
Having in the past worked on engineering infrastructure, I was excited to diversify and work on the product side of a company — I wanted the fulfillment of knowing users were directly impacted by my work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debugging a series of miscalculations in osquery</title>
      <link>https://vishwashah.me/blog/medium/debugging-a-series-of-miscalculations-in-osquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 18:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwashah.me/blog/medium/debugging-a-series-of-miscalculations-in-osquery/</guid>
      <description>Heads up, we’ve moved! If you’d like to continue keeping up with the latest technical content from Square please visit us at our new home https://developer.squareup.com/blog  What is osquery ? osquery is an an open source tool by Facebook that provides a SQL interface for system information.
Over the course of the summer I’ve been working on integrating osquery results into our internal asset tracker for automation/validation purposes. It’s been incredibly useful for monitoring various stats, and the SQL interface makes it easy to use.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>